# **Salvatore Galeotta**

Unity/Unreal Developer

- +44 7519568875
- Brighton
- https://github.com/Adamska-01
- ★ https://adamska-01.github.io/SalvatoreG.github.io/
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/salvator galeotta-10baa9127/

# **SKILLS**

Unreal Engine (C++)

Unity Engine (C#)

Console Development with Unreal

Photon Unity Networking (PUN2)

SDL, DirectX (C/C++)

Familiar with Phyton, SQL

Version control tools (GitHub)

**UI/Gameplay Programming** 

Basic 3D modelling (3DSMax, Blender)

# **EDUCATION**

**BSc (Hons) Computer Games Software Development** Solent University 2019 - 2022 | Southampton, UK

**Electronics Diploma** IISS Augusto Righi 2010 - 2016 | Cerignola, Italy

## PROFILE

I am a Unity/Unreal developer with 1+ years of industry experience. Currently, I am actively engaged in developing an Unreal Demo at West Pier Studio, and I am eager to seize the perfect opportunity to collaborate with a larger development team.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Unity/Unreal Developer**

West Pier Studio (High Up) ☑

Oct 2022 - present | Brighton, UK

- Developed a full vehicle customization system (Parts, colors, liveries) demo in Unreal engine.
- Implementation of blueprints that allow designers to easily create vehicle parts (eventually adding functionalities such as color/livery swap thanks to actor components) and add them to the game.
- Created a fully packaged (portable) version of Unreal with PlayStation 5 build support to speed up the building process.
- Designed and implemented custom UI widgets to overcome Unreal's UI limitations, such as pop-up buttons, bindable widgets, and a carousel system.
- Designed and Implemented a proxy to easily bind widget events without the use of Unreal Functions.
- Developed a custom UI navigation system that works with gamepads.

### **Gameplay Programmer**

Mysteric Studio (Iskandar: The Spear of Truth) ☑

2021 - 2022 | Southempton, UK

- Developed a top-down adventure game using Unity with a team of 15-20 people, including designers and artists.
- Responsible for the implementation of the inventory system (including UI linkage), equipment (with stats update), shop (buy/sell items), loot system, accessories and items functionalities, quest system, and some of the puzzles.

### Gameplay/Asset programmer

SleepyTime Studio (Hypersomnia) □

2021 | Southampton, UK

- Developed a first person horror game using Unity with a team of 8-9
- Responsible for the implementation of player stats, interactable items, player animations, puzzles, and level loader.

## **SOLO PROJECTS**

## **Army's Heaven**

Online FPS

2022 - present

Single Player/Multiplayer FPS game that uses PUN2 (Photon Unity Package) for its multiplayer backend. This game started as a multiplayer project but I am currently focusing on the single-player mode that will provide a campaign of a few hours, and introduce all the mechanics that I will transfer back into the multiplayer mode (such as a new character controller, guns with proper animations, and new shooting mechanics).